<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jjohnst on Hi, I&#39;m Josh</title>
    <link>http://jjohnst.github.io/authors/jjohnst/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Jjohnst on Hi, I&#39;m Josh</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 09:00:00 +0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://jjohnst.github.io/authors/jjohnst/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>5-Bullet Friday</title>
      <link>http://jjohnst.github.io/bullet-posts/may-18-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 09:00:00 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jjohnst.github.io/bullet-posts/may-18-2/</guid>
      <description> Interesting Things  Robert Morris of the Morris Worm and YC These AI phone calls The two philosophies of tech Andrew Ng on Machine Learning and AI The internet in &amp;lsquo;96  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5-Bullet Friday</title>
      <link>http://jjohnst.github.io/bullet-posts/may-18-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 09:00:00 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jjohnst.github.io/bullet-posts/may-18-1/</guid>
      <description> Interesting Things  GM and Tesla Where the Civil War Started and Ended Alexander Graham Bell Recording Bicameral Mind Rap Snacks  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5-Bullet Friday</title>
      <link>http://jjohnst.github.io/bullet-posts/april-18-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 09:00:00 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jjohnst.github.io/bullet-posts/april-18-1/</guid>
      <description> I thought it would be interesting to publish a list of 5 things that I found interesting or liked during the week. I may publish these weekly or wait until I have 5 things to list. I may go back and add context.
Things I Like  Lebron in the playoffs Vietnamese food People who make music in their bedrooms The World After Capital This tool  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anchorman</title>
      <link>http://jjohnst.github.io/posts/anchorman/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2017 09:00:00 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jjohnst.github.io/posts/anchorman/</guid>
      <description>“They tell you the first rule is not to die don’t they?”
“I beg your pardon?”
“When you’re signing the release papers they always tell you that the first rule is not to die because then you can’t go back. I just assumed they told you the same thing.”
He stared at the pretty woman in the black dress, sitting two chairs down the bar, who was apparently speaking to him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Outside the Social Context</title>
      <link>http://jjohnst.github.io/posts/outside-social-context/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2014 09:00:00 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jjohnst.github.io/posts/outside-social-context/</guid>
      <description>When was the last time you took a selfie or posted a status update? For many of us it was no longer than a few hours ago. Today’s technological world revolves around social media and excessive sharing. Our society celebrates uniqueness and individualism but we are never allowed the time to appreciate and explore our own identities without social context. We are constantly broadcasting ourselves to our friends and to the world without ever understanding the impact it has on us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Facebook Has a Content Problem</title>
      <link>http://jjohnst.github.io/posts/facebook-has-a-content-problem/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2014 09:00:00 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jjohnst.github.io/posts/facebook-has-a-content-problem/</guid>
      <description>Note: I began writing this piece several months ago but never got around to finishing it. Some of the news is old, but the idea is still the same.
Several weeks ago I quit Facebook. I know, way to get on the bandwagon, but I really just found that I was not gaining anything from the service, especially the News Feed. However, I was pretty reliant on the messaging component of Facebook, mainly for my friends outside of the U.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>